testmasters.net 2016-10-30

# TestMasters Privacy Policy

### The TestMasters Websites

Thank you for visiting TestMasters. The “TestMasters Websites” include all websites owned and operated by Robin Singh Educational Services, Inc. TestMasters is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our websites, and we want you to be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and how you can update it. By disclosing information to us, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. TestMasters reserves the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please revisit this page periodically to check for modifications. 

### Collected Information

TestMasters collects various types of information from our visitors in order to make adjustments to our websites and to better meet the needs of our users. Some of this information is automatically collected through cookies. Other information is collected when you register for our services and/or order our products. 

### Automatically Collected Non-Personal Information 

Each time you visit one of our websites, your browser or Internet session automatically sends us certain types of non-personal information. This may include information about what browser or what type of computer you use, or information about your operating systems, Internet service provider, or IP address. Our system also automatically gathers information about which areas of our sites you visit and any links on our sites that you use to access other areas of the World Wide Web. We use such information in the aggregate to understand how our visitors use our websites and to make adjustments and improvements. If you would like to have your automatically collected information removed from TestMasters Websites, contact our administrative office. However, if you take our course, purchase our books, or register for any of our services, we will not remove your personal information from our student database, but we will not solicit you or use your information for any purpose other than record-keeping. 

### User Provided Personal Information 

In addition to non-personal information automatically collected by your browser, TestMasters also collects personal information that you provide to us when you register for our products or services, or request information regarding one of our programs. Personal Information may be used for marketing purposes and may result in follow-up communications. If you would like to have your user provided personal information removed from TestMasters Websites, contact our administrative office. However, if you take our course, purchase our books, or register for any of our services, we will not remove your personal information from our student database, but we will not solicit you or use your information for any purpose other than record-keeping. 

TestMasters’ registration sites, the Student Online Resource Center and the Employee Area, require visitors to provide contact information and/or unique identifiers upon registration. Information collected may include a user’s name, address, email address, educational background, year(s) of graduation, as well as unique identifiers, such as their social security numbers or student ID numbers. Contact information is utilized to contact our visitors if necessary. Unique identifiers are employed to verify the user’s identity prior to allowing visitor access to some of our online services. You can choose NOT provide personal information by NOT registering on our websites. While you will be able to access the public portion of our websites, you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

Our payment websites allow customers to request products and services from TestMasters and require visitors to provide contact information and financial information, such as credit card numbers. Contact information is used to send materials to the customer and to contact the customer if necessary. Financial information collected is used to bill the user for the products ordered. You can choose NOT to provide your payment information online. Instead, you can call TestMasters administrative office and provide the personal and financial information required. 

Many of our websites provide users the opportunity to request information from TestMasters. Users must detail what information they would like to receive and provide TestMasters with their contact information which will be used to respond to their request. You can choose NOT to provide this information online. Instead you can call TestMasters and request to have information provided over the phone or mailed to you. 

If you wish to cancel your live course enrollment, TestMasters must receive your withdraw request in writing at our administrative office at least 10 days before the first class meeting. TestMasters will refund your payment within two business days. TestMasters does not allow withdrawals from the online course and all payments towards this class are non-refundable. Your personal information will remain in our student database. You may opt-out of further communications from TestMasters by contacting our administrative office. If you opt-out, we will not solicit you or use your information for any purpose other than record-keeping 

### Transfer of Data to TestMasters in the United States 

Your information may be stored, processed and accessed in the United States or any other countries where TestMasters does business. By using TestMasters Websites and/or TestMasters services, you consent to the transfer of information outside your home country. 

### Directory Information and Aggregate Information

TestMasters respects the privacy of users visiting our websites and will abide by all applicable laws concerning the release of personal information. We may use certain directory information (name, address, phone number and email) that we have collected to send you information about products and services, or updates and other information we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, please inform the TestMasters administrative office. 

Other than directory information you provide us, the data collected as you use TestMasters Websites will be held in strict confidence by the company and will be used for company purposes only. The company may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. However, the individual information you provide us while using the TestMasters Websites will be known only to you and TestMasters. We will not share your personal data with anyone else, except as may be required by law, to enforce the rights of TestMasters in a court of law of competent jurisdiction, or in connection with the sale or transfer of some or all of the assets of TestMasters. 

### Security 

Our websites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We utilize industry standard TLS encryption when accepting your credit card information during the online ordering process. 

### Copyright

Copyright of the TestMasters Websites and all materials included in them are owned by or licensed to Robin Singh Educational Svcs. and all rights are reserved. You must abide by all copyright notices and restrictions contained on the TestMasters Websites. You may not copy, distribute, enter into a database, display, perform, create derivative works of, transmit, or otherwise use any materials from TestMasters Websites (including computer programs or other code). 

### Use of Cookies

On some of our websites, cookies are employed to keep track of your information. A cookie is a small piece of program code stored on your computer that keeps your login information for all of our websites that require you to register, such as our student and employee websites. We do this so you are not required to re-enter your contact information as you move from one of our websites to another. 

### Links

Some TestMasters Websites may contain links to other sites external to TestMasters. When you access these external sites, the providers of the sites will have access to certain information about you. TestMasters is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any sites which we do not directly control. 

### Acceptance of These Terms

By using the TestMasters Websites, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any part of the entire policy, do not use our websites. Your continued use of the TestMasters Websites following the posting of changes to these terms will signify your acceptance of those changes. 

### Definitions

> #### Cookies
> 
> Data created by a web server that is stored on a user’s computer. It provides a way for the website to keep track of a user’s patterns and preferences and, with the cooperation of the Web browser, to store them on the user’s own hard disk. The cookies contain a range of URLs (Web addresses) for which they are valid. When the browser encounters those URLs again, it sends those specific cookies to the web server. You can avoid the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies or warn you before accepting a cookie. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu. 
> 
> **NOTE: If you disable cookies in your browser, you will not be able to access any of TestMasters’ secured websites.**
> 
> #### IP (Internet Protocol) Address
> 
> This is the address of a computer attached to a TCP/IP network. Every client and server station must have a unique IP address. Client workstations have either a permanent address or one that is dynamically assigned for each dial-up session. IP addresses are written as four sets of numbers separated by periods (e.g., 192.168.64.2). 
> 
> #### Browser Session
> 
> A browser session is defined as the period of time a browser is in consecutive use. The session begins when you open the browser and ends when you close it. When you reopen the browser, you begin a new session. 
> 
> #### TLS Encryption (Transport Layer Security)
> 
> TLS Encryption is the leading security protocol on the Internet. When an TLS session is started, the browser sends its public key to the server so that the server can securely send a secret key to the browser. The browser and server exchange data via secret key encryption during that session. We use TLS encryption during registration when you enter your credit card number or other personal information and during the creation of your login for the Online Resource Center when entering your social security number. 
> 
> #### URL (Uniform Resource Locator)
> 
> URLs are Internet addresses. URLs are used to locate sites on the Internet and to navigate between sites and pages within sites. The URL for TestMasters is www.testmasters.net 

TestMasters, The TestMasters Logo, and any other trademarks on the TestMasters Websites are trademarks owned by Robin Singh Educational Services, Inc., DBA TestMasters. You may not use the TestMasters trademarks in connection with any product or service that does not belong to us, or in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among users about whether we are the source, sponsor, or endorser of the product or service, or in any manner that disparages or discredits us. 

The TestMasters Administrative Office  
8383 Wilshire Boulevard  
Suite 742  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211  
1-800-696-5728  
info@testmasters.net 

Complete List of TestMasters Courses  
LSAT Prep Locations

© 1991-2016 TestMasters. All rights reserved.
